and where is the Krakow region
а краковский край где находится
approximately the Krakow region this is the
приблизительно краковский край это вот
Krakow region this is Listen this is the South the south is
краковский край это Слушай это Юг юг
correct the capital of the Krakow region Which
правильно столица краковского края Какая
Krakow probably Krakow is logical Yes you have
Краков наверное Краков логично Да ты
already taught me the capital of the Bratislava region I
меня научил уже столицу Братиславской
will not ask anymore Because
области уже не буду спрашивать Потому
you have already learned yes And where is the
что ты уже научился да А где находится
Bratislava region it is definitely in the
Братиславская область она точно на
west somewhere it is adjacent to the
западе где-то она соседствует с
Krakow
краковски
region yes in the south there
краем да на юге там
Yes I did not
Да я не
know Hello Hello Hello
знал Здравствуйте Здравствуйте
where are you from I am from
Здравствуйте Вы откуда Я с России
mother Russia I can see that you are from Russia by your face what
матушки я вижу что вы из России по лицу
city is Samara Cool And who is a
город какой Самар Прикольно А кто
Tatar
татарин
Chuvash
чуваш россиянин
Russian Russian well you do not look like a Russian so
русский ну на русского не похожи так
Why where are your ancestors from you yourself
Почему откуда у вас предки в сама
came I myself came to Samara from
приехали я сам приехал в Самару вот не
where 3 years ago where I
откуда 3 года назад откуда я отда
came from give all the geography to you tell you
приехал всю географию тебе рассказать
yes Can I not I will
да А можно я не буду
not And where are you from Ukraine
нельзя А ты откуда с Украины
podoli What does this mean the region is like that
подоли Это что значит регион такой
and well
а хорошо
then where did you come to
то откуда приехали в
Samara from the
Самару с
Urals more
Урал
specifically I see that you I see
конкретнее Я же вижу что ты Я же вижу
that you are a Turk Bashkor Tatar Who are
что ты тюрк башкор татарин Кто
you and if I were a Tatar then  what's
ты а если бы я был татарин то что ну
interesting about Tatarstan with you
интересно о Татарстане с тобой бы пол
I can tell you half of your story about Tatarstan
твоей истории я тебе могу за Татарстан
I'm from Russia and Tatarstan
рассказать Я же с России а Татарстан -
is part of Russia super Maybe you can
это часть России супер Может вы мне ещё
tell me about Khakassia it's part of
о Хакасии расскажете это же часть
Russia Yes I can tell you about anything you want
России Да я тебе о чём хочешь могу
where is
рассказать где находится где находится
Khakassia in Russia
Хакасия в России
where is the capital of Khakassia
где столица Хакасии
what And what's the difference to you the city of
какая А какая у тебя разница город
Abakan you don't know anymore You don't even
Абакан о уже не знаешь Ты же даже не
know but you're from Russia you don't know well
знаешь но ты из России не знаешь хорошо
and the capital of the Republic of Tuva Tuva
а столица республики
Yes Tuva and Tuva it is the Republic of
тывы тывы Да Тыва а Тыва оно Республики
which Republic of
какой республики
Tuva also
тывы ещё и
ru it's a good region what kind of capital
ру это край хороший какое какая столица
damn you don't remember everything Kizil Kizil Kizil yes and the
блин не помнишь все Кизил Кизил Кизил да
capital of this Let's go Kalmykia
то а столица этой Давай Калмыкии
Republic of
Республики
Kalmykia is closer to you to Samara
Калмыкия это ближе к тебе к Самаре
Yes remind me the first letter e e eshkere e
Да напомни первую букву э э эшкере э
Elista
Элиста
Elista really Yes Elista Cool Listen damn
Элиста реально Да Элиста Круто Слушай ты
Interesting so let's go again let's go again Let's
блин Интересно так давай ещё давай ещё
chase you the capital of the Republic of
Погоняем тебя столица республики
Ingushetia
Ингушетия
Ingushetia there is a capital they have Well
ингушети там есть столица у них Да ну у
every Republic has a capital starting with m starting with
каждой Республики есть столица на м на
m  m
букву м м
Makhachkala Magas Magas
Махачкала Магас Магас
bku you
бку ты ВС
know everything yes Geographer specialist in the
знаешь да Географ специалист по
collapse specialist in the collapse of the Russian
развалу специалист по развалу Российской
Federation Lord Why do you need
Федерации Господи Зачем тебе
this and the capital of the Altai
это а столица Алтайского
Territory of the Altai Territory damn Altai Territory is
края Алтайского края блин Алтайский край
beautiful probably there this
красивый наверное там этот
[music]
[музыка]
say the first letter and say the second here
скажи а вторую скажи вот
WTO ba say the third
ВТО ба третью скажи
now Barnau
сейчас барнау
Barnau I know all this and next look
барнау я всё это знаю а рядом смотри
next to slm
рядом
Krai
слм краем
Altai Republic it has what
Республика Алтай у неё какая
capital next to the Altai Republic I immediately
столица рядом с Республика Алтай Сразу
say the first three letters of the mountains Mountain
говорю первых три буквы
Altai
гор Горный Алтай
Gornoaltaysk Eh you didn't guess almost well a
Горноалтайск Эх ты не угадал почти ну
little bit was nearby Imagine So come on the
чуть-чуть рядом был Прикинь Так давай
capital of
столица
Udmurtia
Удмуртии
Udmurtia is a good region do
Удмуртия хороший край
n't you know about your Russia now so
не знаешь про сво Росси сча такой
impudent I am I Come on the capital of Udmurtia Yes I don't
дерзкий я я Давай столица Удмуртии Да я
know
не знаю
Udmurtia Izhevsk for sure Yes I know yes the
удмуртию Ижевск точно Да я знаю да
capital of Maria L What Yash Korla Damn
столица Марии Л Какая Яш корла Во блин У
you have one point listen you know why I
вас один балл слушай знаешь почему я
know because I was in this city I
знаю потому что я был в этом городе я 8
traveled for 8 years Around Russia and all
лет ездил По России и все
those All those  The
те Все те
republics that you named Yes, I have
Республики которые ты назвал Да там я в
never
них ни разу не
been there, it is good, the capital of
был хорошо столица
Buryatia, Buryatia, I know
Бурятии Бурятии Я знаю
Yes, you know, I howled
Да вот знаешь я
Irku no no no no, not Irkutsk Irkutsk
Ирку нет нет нет нет не Иркутск Иркутск
Irku, don't wait, in Buryatia, the capital of Irku
Ирку не подожди в Бурятии столи
Why are you doing that? It is not
Ирку Зачем ты так делаешь Не есть
Irkutsk And this is the capital of the Irkutsk region, and
Иркутск А это столица Иркутской области
Buryatia has Irku Irku
а у Бурятии Ирку Ирку
ud, the capital of Buryatia, Ulan Yes, Ulan, you know, you know, so Ulan yes,
уд столица Бурятии Улана Да Улана е
so look,
шаришь шаришь так Улана да да так смотри
we are you, so the capital of the Jewish Autonomous
мы тебя так столица Еврейской автономной
Region Oh, I don't know there at all, I don't think at all, I
области Ой там вообще не знаю я вообще
found out on Biro, it starts on
не думаю узнал на биро начинается на
Bidjan, it ends in
Биджан заканчивается
Birabidjan, super, yes, yes, I heard, I understood, the
Бирабиджан супер да да слышал понял
capital of
столица
Balochistan, what is
белуджистан что
Balochistan, and who lives there, is it in
белуджистан а кто там живёт это что в
Russia? Come in, yes, Balochistan, yes, between
Россию Входи да белуджистан да между
Dagestan and
дагестаном и
Ingushetia, no, I don't know for sure, no, no, go, go, go,
ингушетией не я точно не знаю не не го
yes, and what nationalities
Гори гори да А какие там национальности
live there, Balochistan, Balochistan, Balochistan,
живут белуджи белуджи белуджи
Yes, there is no one here, Samari  I have never
Да никого нет вот здесь самари я ни разу
heard of I
не слышал Я
Belgi And you know everyone in Ukraine yours
Белджи А ты знаешь всех в Украине свои
yes And you probably call a few Come on let's call you the
да А вас немного наверное называй Давай
capital of some region
давай столицу какой-то области я тебе
Yes I don't know the region I
буду называть Да я не знаю областя Я
know half and I
знаю полови и
understood everything there Western Northern Southern I
всё понял там Западная Северная Южная
know what it is for you so and the capital of
знаю это какая у вас так а столица
Kabardina
кабардина
Balkaria
Балкарии
Ah Nalchik well olki Well you are generally Nalchik a
Ах Нальчик ну ёлки Ну ты вообще Нальчик
boy so and in short Eva Circassia Do you
мальчик так а короча Ева Черкесии А
want me to explain to you why I don't know
хочешь я тебе объясню почему я не знаю
these steel why explain the
эти стали почему объясни
excuse No not an excuse Probably this is a
отмазку Да не отмазка Наверное это
problem Well the problem of
проблема Ну проблема
our education system
нашего системы обучения
Yes I probably think that we are not
Да я наверное думаю что нам мало
taught enough this geography we have never seen a map of
преподают эту географию карту не видели
Russia Yes
России никогда
I have seen a map of the country I
Да карту страны то я видел Я те я тебе
can tell you the southwest
могу сказать юго-запад
northeast it is
северо-восток это
but good Which region of Russia Do you know
но хорошо Какой регион России Ты знаешь
know what the problem is I was not
зна в чём проблема Не я сейчас
preparing to philosophize specifically now voo Well maybe you
готовился специально воо Ну может быть
remember geography well people
запоминаешь географию хоро же люди
who remember all the geography You
которые помнят всю географию Вот ты
remember all the geography I never
помнишь всю географию вот я никогда не
set a goal to know everything there the capitals of the
задавался цель знать все там столицы
regions I don't know either I never set a goal But
регионов не зна тоже не задавался Но
somehow they
както их
know Well by
зна Ну бы
earning is not the point I think it is
зарабо это не суть Я считаю что это
not important Well maybe from one point of
неважно Ну может быть с одной точки
view it is important to know Well well well and if
зрения важно знать Да ну ну ну а если бы
I knew this so that there is a lot of text in general a lot of
я знал это чтоб много текста вообще
text just Well look I am
очень много текста просто Ну смотри я
telling you that if I knew
тебе говорю о том что если бы я ну знал
and did not know what would it change of
и не знал что бы это меняло в
course Uva I do
конечно Ува эре
nt
не
know This is your Russian Federation Yes it is
знаю Это же твоя Российская Федерация Да
huge Gomel
она огромная Гомель
Gomel I know the nearest capital where I
Гомель Я я знаю столиц ближайший где Я
grew up where I grew up where I was where I went where I
рос где я вырос где я был где я ездил
drove there where I heard where What
где я там проезжал где я слышал где Что
maybe you see I am now today
может быть понимаешь я сечас сегодня
Saturday
субо
3 am my brain is already so
3 ночи у меня мозг настолько уже
rested that I dont want to talk
отдыхает что я вообще не хочу говорить
about geography at all Maybe I thought I
про географию Может быть я е подумал
remembered but this in no way
вспомнил но это ни в коем случае не
means that I do not respect my
говорит о том что я не уважаю свою
country and do not respect the people who live in this
страну и не уважаю народ который в этой
country I them all Well
стране который живёт Я их всех
okay and the capital of the Lublin region
Ну хорошо а столица люблинской области
Lublinsky Lublin region Yes I dont
Люблинский люблинской области Да я не
know the capital of the regions there are many Lublin
знаю столицу областей их же много Люблин
if the region is Lublin then Lublin is a
если область Люблинская то Люблин это ж
region Well well well yes I agree And where is
области Ну ну да ну да согласен А где
it approximately located can you
она приблизительно находится можешь
remember  Lublin
вспомнить Люблинская
region It's probably small Somewhere
область Она наверное маленькая где-то
probably if Lublin region I
наверно ем если Люблинская область Я
think that it's to the west To the
думаю что она на
west To the east To the
запа на западо Востоке на
west It can't be like that
западо Не может быть
Lublin region Well somewhere
такого Люблинская область Ну где-то
maybe
может быть
West West northwest somewhere in
Запада Запад северо-запад вот где-то в
that northwest Right yeah Right
то северозапад Правильно да Правильно
Probably because I
Наверно потому что я чу по
wanted to hear about the regions yeah me west east
областям хотел да меня западо востоком
Yeah yeah I already joked yeah and Krakow region
Да ть так уже пошутил да а краковский
where is
край где находится
Krakow region approximately this is Krakow region
приблизительно краковский край это вот
- this is Listen this is South south
краковский край - это Слушай это Юг юг
right South south -
правильно Юг юг -
this is Listen this is Krakow region this is
это Слушай это краковский край это
somewhere closer to you there yeah Not
где-то ближе к вам туда да Не
really I wasn't there and didn't hear
совсем я не был там и не слышал
south Yes Rakow region Damn listen
юг Да раковский край Блин слушай не был
I wasn't there I didn't hear anything Listen how
Я там я ничего не слышал Слушай как
How many problems we have it turns out that Well
Сколько проблем у нас оказывается что Ну
look this is the south it borders with
смотри это юг он граничит с
Krasnodar and Stavropol but it's
краснодарским и ставропольским но он
small south Krasnodar
небольшой юг краснодарский
Stavropol sky Capital Capital of
ставропольский небо Столица Столица
Krakow region What Krakow probably
краковского края Какая Краков наверное
Krakow is logical Yes you've already taught me everything
Краков логично Да ты меня научил уже всё
yeah because you know history this is
да по что Потому что знаешь историю это
about  Cossacks, it seems, were there some Yes Cossacks
о казаки вроде там были какие Да Казаки
and there is a kind of history, like, there is such a
и там типа история типа есть такая ну
Legend that Well, in this city of Krakow in the
Легенда что Ну в этом городе Краков в
Krakow region there is the Wawel Castle
краковском крае есть вавельский замок
that there was a Dragon and his hero, like,
что там был Дракон и его богатыр типа
won, super cool, didn't know su If
победил супер круто не знал су Если
you are in the south, like, where Krasnodar,
будешь на югах типа там где Краснодар
like, you will definitely stop by Krakow
типа ста заедете обязательно в Краков
Look, they have a very interesting swing,
Посмотри у них очень замах интересный
damn, cool
блин кру
I didn't know such moments And do you
я не знал такие моменты а Пермский край
know where Perm Krai is Well, Perm Krai, then yes,
знаешь где находится Ну Пермский край то
Perm is right here, not Perm, there is
да Перм вот тут рядышком не есть Перм
Perm Krai Well, Perm Krai
есть Пермский Край ну Пермский край -
is like a region and a capital, so to speak,
это как область и столица так скажем
before the capital is Well, you see, you say a little bit, the capital Well,
перед столица это Ну видишь ты немножко
maybe that's
говоришь столица Ну может быть это
right, it sounds kind of cool, a regional
правильно както круто звучит областной
city That's how we
город Вот так мы
say a regional city, let's say Perms
говорим областной город допустим пермс
there or Orenburg region, the regional
там или Оренбургская область областной
city of Orenburg, that is, the key one, well,
город Оренбург то есть ключевой вот
interesting, but
так ну интересно а вот
Okay, let's talk about geography If you
Хорошо давай вот по географии Если ты
know Chukotka Where is it in the north And
знаешь Чукотка Где находится на севере А
where
где
exactly is Chukotka Krai, probably
именно Чукотский край наверное
this is
этот этоже
IT, this is the
ИТ это
northeast, there is the northeast  over
северо-восток там северо-восток над
Kamchatka over Kamchatka yes it's far it's
камчаткой над Камчатка да это далеко это
very far like closer to Alaska it
очень далеко типа ближе к Аляске
turns out chuk in short Mrs. Anadyr the
получается чук короче г жи Анадырь
capital Adyr yes
столица адыр
we have a huge huge not a
дака у нас огромнейшая огромная не
huge country om we do
страна огромная ом
n't even know you see how good it is that
даже не знаем видишь как вот ты хорошо
you talk about this and it seems to me that
что ты об этом говоришь и мне кажется
this topic needs to be raised in order to
эту тему надо поднять чтобы
talk about this there are a lot of problems and uh uh well that the
вот об этом говорить проблем много а э э
center the capital of the Bratislava
ну та центр столицу Братиславской
region I won't ask anymore Because
области уже не буду спрашивать Потому
you've already learned yes And where is the
что ты уже научился да А где находится
Bratislava region and the Bratislava
Братиславская область а Братиславская
region most likely is not Russia not Russia Russia Russia Bratislava
область скорее всего это не Россия не
probably where is
Россия Россия Россия Братиславе наверное
Bratislava Well, where is the Bratislava
Братислава Да ну а где Братиславская
region Well it's definitely in the west somewhere
область Ну она точно на западе где-то
it borders on the Krakow region on
она соседствует с краковский краем на
this in the south there
это на юге там
Yes I didn't know under the Caucasus Yes it
Да я не знал под кавказом Да там
turns out there is like the Caucasus
получается типа как есть вот Кавказский
ridge Stavropol region Krasnodar region
хребет Ставропольский край Краснодарский
and between them there is also Rakovsky yes
край и между ними ещё есть раковский да
Bratislavsky
Братиславский
Bratislava the capital of Slovakia actually Well is there
Братиславе столица Словакии вообще-то Ну
one city called that and
есть ли что один город так называется и
what well Slovakia It's not Russia there is
что ну Словакия Это же не Россия есть
Slovakia  and Bratislava and the Bratislava
Словакия и Братислава а Братиславская
region in Russia
область в России
Bratislava what
Братиславская кая
region now I'll google it right I googled it
область сейчас загуглю прям я загугли
interestingly near the Krakow region
интересно возле краковского края
Bratislava
братиславу
Bratislava google the
Братислава загугли краковский край
Krakow region the Krakow region is nearby there like on the map it
краковский край рядом там типа на карте
will be anyway Bratislava region
будет по-любому Братиславская область
Krakow
краковский
[laughter]
[смех]
Kraikov
крайковский
region Rakov Oh listen beautiful city so
край раков О слушай красивый город так
from the photos
по фоткам
Krakow region now
краковский край сейчас
map
карт
map so Krakow main in
карта так Краков главный
short train
короче
station
вокзал
Listen he generally shows me
Слушай он мне вообще показывает
as the capital Krakow Krakow
как столица Краков краковский
region all this time at home
край всё это время на дом
[music]
[музыка]
corner Krakow moldov region moldov
угола Краков молдов область молдов
region right
область правильно
and you're sitting like that Well these are all Slavic
а ты такой сидишь Ну это славянские все
cities Well Okay okay mo moldov
города Ну О'кей Ладно мо молдов ся
region where is it Well here Krakow you are on Google
область где это Ну вот Краков ты на Goog
where is it Well it's already behind you there
где он находится Ну он уже за вами там
somewhere behind Kiev Well as you correctly
где-то за Киевом Ну как ты правильно
said moldov region No no it's
сказал молдов ся область Да нет это не
not moldov And what region Well yes moldov region
не молдов А какая область А ну да молдов
Yes moldov region Yes Probably it's in
ся Да молдов ся область Да Наверно это в
Romania in
Румынии в
Ruh
Рух
you Well yes
ты Ну да
you agree  I was taken for a ride,
согласен ты меня прокатил прокатил Да я
taken for a ride Yes, I came up with Barnaul yes, well,
придумал да да ну с таким за пилом
of course you're sitting at a serious saw with such a one It wasn't just me who
конечно серьёзным сидишь Не я просто
went I'll come up with you like that
пошёл я та я тако придумаю тебя так
Altai Krai like you say letters I say
Алтайский край типа ты говоришь буквы я
letters b you say ru I yes I'll come up with
говорю буквы б ты говоришь ру я да я
letters
придумаю буквы
I'll come up with letters on the go In
Я придумаю буквы на ходу
short, just like Kabardina Balkaria
Короче так же как кабардина Балкария
came up with
придумал
Nalchik Well, how
Нальчик Ну
great are you if it's bad Well, listen to the Krakow
молодец раз плохо Ну слушай краковской
region in general well you're like you I'm just
области вообще ну ты так ты я я просто
now UMO is not the Krakow region wait not the
сейчас УМО не краковский край подожди не
Bratislava region
область Братиславская
How many regions Yes, at least I'll
Сколько областей Да хотя бы
look How many
посмотрю Сколько
regions regions are in
областей областей в
Russia ROSI
России РОСИ
48 Well,
48 Ну
yes, yes, a huge country what can I say is
да да огромная страна что говорить
huge to say that's why another
огромна говорить поэтому вот ещё
worker Bugaisky wrote a book on the
работни бугайский написал книжку
dismemberment of
расчленение
Russia that it's somehow too huge,
Росси что она что-то слишком огромная
too aggressive, it needs to be divided
слишком агрессивная надо её разделить
because you don't even know your
потому что вы даже не знаете свою
geography Yes, you don't know where it is,
географию Да не знаете где же находится
why do you need such a big country, you need to
зачем вам такая большая страна нужно её
divide it into different states Let
разделить на разные государства Пусть
them be separately small and not
они будут отдельно маленькие и никого не
bother anyone Glory to Ukraine No, no,
будут трогать Слава Украине Да не не
no,
не
like it was divine when he started
лайк ко было божественно когда он начал
google krako what a beautiful city
гуглить крако вот какой красивый город
Yes the castle here so I think write on y
Да замок тут так я думаю пись на й
Telegram right now axis VN a
Telegram прям зараз ось ВН а
Popik this is very and very important YouTube is
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
busy with us through scarg or in ny ban and very
заня нас через скарг ор в ньй бан и дуже
many videos are not shown to people at times do not
багато видео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about streams so that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
we Mali operational links are
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
written right now and there in telegram we will
пишиться прямо зараз а к там в телеграми
find videos also interesting and useful
окрим видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we owe you
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
constant operational links
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
letter a
пись а